(Raj:)So... couldn't help
but notice none of you RSVP'd
(Raj:)to my murder mystery dinner party.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah.
We were meaning to do that.
(Raj:)No, you weren't, because it
was a weak ago and nobody came!
(Raj:)So if you want to solve the mystery
of who stabbed Koothrappali
(Raj:)in the back with the weapon of
indifference, it was all of you.
I don't think that qualities
as a mystery.
(Sheldon:)We all knew what we were doing.
(Amy:)-We're sorry, Rajesh.
-Maybe we can do it next week.
(Howard:)Whoa, we're not that sorry.
(Raj:)Don't worry, I can take a hint.
No more murder mystery parties.
(Sheldon:)-Thank you.
-Hallelujah.
(Raj:)Because I've got something
even better planned!
-Come on!
-Just hear me out.
(Raj:)I'm going to make you guys
a scavenger hunt.
(Raj:)like they have at MIT.
(Howard:)Oh, I loved those.
I did them every year there.
(Leonard:)-We did them at Princeton, too.
-Oh, that's cute.
(Howard:)Like it's a real college.
(Sheldon:)That's amusing. I was going
to say that about MIT,